Guide to the National Education Association-Conventions records, 1857-1998 NEA1008.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Conventions and Conferences, Bulk, 1970-1996 1858-1998; 1970-1996; Series 1; National Education Association of the United States. Meeting.; 85 Linear Feet
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-State Coordinators [file 1/4], 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1438, Folder 7)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-State Coordinators [file 2/4], 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1439, Folder 1)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-State Coordinators [file 3/4], 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1439, Folder 2)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-State Coordinators [file 4/4], 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1439, Folder 3)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-State Coordinators Assembly, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1439, Folder 4)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-State Housing List, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1439, Folder 5)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Telephone, Series 1 (Box 1439, Folder 6)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Transportation/Tours, 1988-1990; Series 1 (Box 1439, Folder 7)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-VIPs, Series 1 (Box 1439, Folder 8)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Voting, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1439, Folder 9)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Adjustment Changes, Series 1 (Box 1440, Folder 4)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Adjustment Points (State Housing Lists), 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1440, Folder 5)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Annual Meeting Guide, Series 1 (Box 1440, Folder 6)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Arts and Entertainment Guide, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1440, Folder 7)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Campground, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1440, Folder 8)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Caucus-Respect Life, Series 1 (Box 1440, Folder 9)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Computers, Series 1 (Box 1441, Folder 1)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Convention Bureau, 1990-1992; Series 1 (Box 1441, Folder 2)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Convention Hall, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1441, Folder 3)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Convention Site, 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 1441, Folder 4)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Delegate Packet Mailing, Series 1 (Box 1441, Folder 5)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Entertainment, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1441, Folder 6)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Exhibits [file 1/2], 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1441, Folder 7)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Exhibits [file 2/2], 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1441, Folder 8)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Exhibit Packet, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1441, Folder 9)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Friendship Night, Series 1 (Box 1441, Folder 10)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Guides [file 1/3], 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1441, Folder 11)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Guides [file 2/3], 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1442, Folder 1)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Guides [file 3/3], 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1442, Folder 2)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Host Committee [file 1/4], 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1442, Folder 3)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Host Committee [file 2/4], 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1442, Folder 4)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Host Committee [file 3/4], 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1442, Folder 5)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Host Committee [file 4/4], 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1442, Folder 6)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Airport Hilton, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1443, Folder 1)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Alexandra, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1443, Folder 2)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Avalon, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1443, Folder 3)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Best Western-Airport, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1443, Folder 4)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Biltmore Hotel, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1443, Folder 5)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Castle, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1443, Folder 6)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Contracts [file 1/2], 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1443, Folder 7)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Contracts [file 2/2], 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1443, Folder 8)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Days Inn, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1443, Folder 9)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Deauville, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1443, Folder 10)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Desertland Inn Surfside, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1443, Folder 11)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Dilido Beach Hotel, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1444, Folder 1)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Diplomat, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1444, Folder 2)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Doral Country Club, 1990-1992; Series 1 (Box 1444, Folder 3)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Doral Hotel-On the Ocean, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1444, Folder 4)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Dupont Plaza Hotel, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1444, Folder 5)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Eden Roc, 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 1444, Folder 6)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Embassy Suites, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1444, Folder 7)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Embassy Suites-Airport, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1444, Folder 8)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-General, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1444, Folder 9)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Grand Bay Hotel, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1445, Folder 1)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Hilton-Fountainbleu [file 1/2], 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1445, Folder 2)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Hilton-Fountainbleu [file 2/2], 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1445, Folder 3)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Airport, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1445, Folder 4)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Airport-50 Lakes, Series 1 (Box 1445, Folder 5)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Le Jeune, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1445, Folder 6)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Newport Pier, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1445, Folder 7)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Oceanside, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1445, Folder 8)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Howard Johnson-Alton Road, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1445, Folder 9)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Howard Johnson-Convention Center, 1988-1991; Series 1 (Box 1445, Folder 10)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Hyatt Regency, 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 1446, Folder 1)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Inn on the Bay, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1446, Folder 2)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Inter Continental, 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 1446, Folder 3)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Marco Polo Hotel, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1446, Folder 4)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Marriot, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1446, Folder 5)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Marriot-Biscayne Bay, 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 1446, Folder 6)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Miami Lakes Inn, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1446, Folder 7)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Omni International [file 1/2], 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1446, Folder 8)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Omni International [file 2/2], 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1447, Folder 1)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Project Equality, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1447, Folder 2)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Quality Inn Convention Center, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1447, Folder 3)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Quality Inn-Surfside Beach, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1447, Folder 4)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Radisson Mart Plaza, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1447, Folder 5)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Ramada-Airport, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1447, Folder 6)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Ritz Plaza, Series 1 (Box 1447, Folder 7)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Roney Plaza, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1447, Folder 8)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Sans Souci, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1447, Folder 9)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Seacoast, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1447, Folder 10)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Seville Hotel, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1447, Folder 11)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Shawnee (Ramada), 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 1447, Folder 12)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Shelbourne Beach, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1448, Folder 1)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Sheraton Bal. Harbor, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1448, Folder 2)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Sheraton Brickell Point, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1448, Folder 3)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Sheraton River House, 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 1448, Folder 4)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Sofitel, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1448, Folder 5)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Hotels-Soverign, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1448, Folder 6)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Information Booth, Series 1 (Box 1448, Folder 7)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Magazine [file 1/3], 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1448, Folder 8)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Magazine [file 2/3], 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1448, Folder 9)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Magazine [file 3/3], 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1449, Folder 1)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Meeting Planners Guide, Series 1 (Box 1449, Folder 2)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Minority/Joint Conference, Series 1 (Box 1449, Folder 3)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Miscellaneous [file 1/3], 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 1449, Folder 4)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Miscellaneous [file 2/3], 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 1449, Folder 5)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Miscellaneous [file 3/3], 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 1449, Folder 6)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Miscellaneous Matters Pertaining to Convention, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1449, Folder 7)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Music Licensing, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1449, Folder 8)
  - 1991- Miami Beach, FL- NEA Mobilizes for Action: Advancing the Nation's Education Agenda- 129th Annual Meeting, July 2-7, 1991; Series 1 (Box 4632, Folder 3)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-NEA Task Force, Series 1 (Box 1449, Folder 9)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Non-Profit Fundraiser [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1449, Folder 10)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Non-Profit Fundraiser [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1450, Folder 1)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Physically Challenged, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1450, Folder 2)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Picker-Uppers, 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 1450, Folder 3)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Recycling, Series 1 (Box 1450, Folder 4)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-"RA Today", 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1450, Folder 5)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Runners, Series 1 (Box 1450, Folder 6)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Site Inspection, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1450, Folder 7)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-State Coordinators [file 1/6], 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 1450, Folder 8)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-State Coordinators [file 2/6], 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 1450, Folder 9)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-State Coordinators [file 3/6], 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 1451, Folder 1)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-State Coordinators [file 4/6], 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 1451, Folder 2)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-State Coordinators [file 5/6], 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 1451, Folder 3)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-State Coordinators [file 6/6], 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 1451, Folder 4)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-State Coordinators Assembly, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1451, Folder 5)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Tours/Special Events, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1451, Folder 6)
  - 1991-Miami, FL-Uniserv, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1451, Folder 7)
  - 1991 State Education Editors Annual Meeting, June 1991; series 1 (Box 4398, Folder 29)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Amusements, Series 1 (Box 1452, Folder 1)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Badges, Series 1 (Box 1452, Folder 2)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Budget, 1990-1992; Series 1 (Box 1452, Folder 3)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Busing, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1452, Folder 4)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Campaign Candidates, 1991-1992; Series 1 (Box 1452, Folder 5)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Camping, Series 1 (Box 1452, Folder 6)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Clinton, Bill Visit, Series 1 (Box 1452, Folder 7)
    Clinton, Bill
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Contracts, 1991-1992; Series 1 (Box 1452, Folder 8)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Convention Agreement and Schedule, Series 1 (Box 1452, Folder 9)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Convention Center Services [file 1/2], 1990-1992; Series 1 (Box 1452, Folder 10)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Convention Center Services [file 2/2], 1990-1992; Series 1 (Box 1452, Folder 11)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Convention Hall-Contracts, 1985-1992; Series 1 (Box 1452, Folder 12)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Correspondence-Convention Hall, 1989-1992; Series 1 (Box 1452, Folder 13)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Correspondence-Hotels, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1452, Folder 14)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Delegate Mailing [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1453, Folder 1)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Delegate Mailing [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1453, Folder 2)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Delegate Report, Series 1 (Box 1453, Folder 3)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Delegate Seating, Series 1 (Box 1453, Folder 4)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Demonstrations, Series 1 (Box 1453, Folder 5)
  - 1992-Washington, DC- Elections 1992: New Priorities for Children- 130th Annual Meeting, July 3-8, 1992; Series 1 (Box 4632, Folder 4)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Evaluation, Series 1 (Box 1453, Folder 6)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Exhibitors [file 1/6], 1991-1992; Series 1 (Box 1453, Folder 7)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Exhibitors [file 2/6], 1991-1992; Series 1 (Box 1453, Folder 8)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Exhibitors [file 3/6], 1991-1992; Series 1 (Box 1454, Folder 1)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Exhibitors [file 4/6], 1991-1992; Series 1 (Box 1454, Folder 2)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Exhibitors [file 5/6], 1991-1992; Series 1 (Box 1454, Folder 3)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Exhibitors [file 6/6], 1991-1992; Series 1 (Box 1454, Folder 4)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Floor Plans [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1454, Folder 5)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Floor Plans [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1455, Folder 1)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Food Service, Series 1 (Box 1455, Folder 2)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Friendship Night, Series 1 (Box 1455, Folder 3)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Host Committee [file 1/2], 1991-1992; Series 1 (Box 1455, Folder 4)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Host Committee [file 2/2], 1991-1992; Series 1 (Box 1455, Folder 5)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-ANA, 1990-1992; Series 1 (Box 1455, Folder 6)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Capitol Hilton, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1455, Folder 7)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Crystal City Marriot, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1456, Folder 1)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Crystal Gateway, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1456, Folder 2)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Dupont Plaza Hotel, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1456, Folder 3)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Embassy Row Hotel, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1456, Folder 4)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Embassy Suites-Downtown, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1456, Folder 5)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-General, 1990-1992; Series 1 (Box 1456, Folder 6)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Governor's House-Holiday Inn, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1456, Folder 7)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Grand Hyatt Washington, 1990-1992; Series 1 (Box 1456, Folder 8)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Highland Hotel, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1456, Folder 9)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Capitol, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1456, Folder 10)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Central, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1456, Folder 11)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Crowne Plaza, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1456, Folder 12)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Holiday Inn-National Airport, 1990-1992; Series 1 (Box 1456, Folder 13)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Hyatt Regency-Capitol Hill, 1991; Series 1 (Box 1457, Folder 1)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Hyatt Regency-Crystal City, 1990-1992; Series 1 (Box 1457, Folder 2)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Loews L'Enfant Plaza Hotel, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1457, Folder 3)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Marriott-Washington, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1457, Folder 4)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Mayflower Stouffer Hotel, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1457, Folder 5)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Omni Georgetown Hotel, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1457, Folder 6)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Omni Shoreham Hotel, 1989-1992; Series 1 (Box 1457, Folder 7)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Quality Hotel-Capitol Hill, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1457, Folder 8)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Radisson Park Terrace Hotel, 1990-1992; Series 1 (Box 1457, Folder 9)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Ritz-Carlton Hotel, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1457, Folder 10)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Sheraton, 1990-1992; Series 1 (Box 1458, Folder 1)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Sheraton Carlton Hotel, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1458, Folder 2)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Washington Court Hotel, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1458, Folder 3)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Washington Hilton and Towers, 1990-1992; Series 1 (Box 1458, Folder 4)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Washington Plaza Hotel, 1990-1992; Series 1 (Box 1458, Folder 5)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Hotels-Westin Hotel, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1458, Folder 6)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Materials Delivery, Series 1 (Box 1458, Folder 7)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Medical Services, Series 1 (Box 1458, Folder 8)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Miscellaneous, Series 1 (Box 1458, Folder 9)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Non-Profit Fundrasier, Series 1 (Box 1458, Folder 10)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Portfolio/Booklet Orders Received [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1459, Folder 1)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Portfolio/Booklet Orders Received [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1459, Folder 2)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Program, Series 1 (Box 1459, Folder 3)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Program/Platform Guests, Series 1 (Box 1459, Folder 4)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Physically Challenged, 1991-1992; Series 1 (Box 1459, Folder 5)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-"R.A. Today", Series 1 (Box 1459, Folder 6)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Restaurant Survey [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1459, Folder 7)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Restaurant Survey [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1460, Folder 1)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Room Pick Up, Series 1 (Box 1460, Folder 2)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Security, Series 1 (Box 1460, Folder 3)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Staff, Series 1 (Box 1460, Folder 4)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-State Coordinators [file 1/2], 1991-1992; Series 1 (Box 1460, Folder 5)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-State Coordinators [file 2/2], 1991-1992; Series 1 (Box 1460, Folder 6)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-State Orders for Portfolios/Guides, 1992-1993; Series 1 (Box 1460, Folder 7)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-VIPs, Series 1 (Box 1460, Folder 8)
  - 1992-Washington, DC-Voting, Series 1 (Box 1460, Folder 9)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Budget, 1991-1993; Series 1 (Box 1461, Folder 1)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Camping, Series 1 (Box 1461, Folder 2)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Caucus-Special Interest, Series 1 (Box 1461, Folder 3)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Convention Agreements, 1992; Series 1 (Box 1461, Folder 4)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Convention Hall-Contract, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1461, Folder 5)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Correspondence-Convention Bureau, 1986-1991; Series 1 (Box 1461, Folder 6)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Correspondence-Miscellaneous, 1992-1993; Series 1 (Box 1461, Folder 7)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Delegate Materials, Series 1 (Box 1461, Folder 8)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Delegate Packet, Series 1 (Box 1461, Folder 9)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Delegate Survey, Series 1 (Box 1461, Folder 10)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Directory, Series 1 (Box 1462, Folder 1)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Exhibits [file 1/3], 1992-1993; Series 1 (Box 1462, Folder 2)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Exhibits [file 2/3], 1992-1993; Series 1 (Box 1462, Folder 3)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Exhibits [file 3/3], 1992-1993; Series 1 (Box 1462, Folder 4)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Exhibits Information, Series 1 (Box 1462, Folder 5)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Floor Plan, Series 1 (Box 1462, Folder 6)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Food Service, 1986-1993; Series 1 (Box 1462, Folder 7)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Guide, Series 1 (Box 1462, Folder 8)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Host Committee, 1992-1993; Series 1 (Box 1463, Folder 1)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotel Information, Series 1 (Box 1463, Folder 2)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotel Pickups, Series 1 (Box 1463, Folder 3)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Airport Hilton, 1991; Series 1 (Box 1463, Folder 4)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-ANA Hotel, 1990-1992; Series 1 (Box 1463, Folder 5)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Cathedral Hill Hilton, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1463, Folder 6)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Clarion Hotel, 1991-1992; Series 1 (Box 1463, Folder 7)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Fairmont Hotel, 1988-1993; Series 1 (Box 1463, Folder 8)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-General, 1989-1992; Series 1 (Box 1463, Folder 9)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Grand Hyatt on Union Square, 1989-1992; Series 1 (Box 1464, Folder 1)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Hilton on Hilton Square, 1988-1993; Series 1 (Box 1464, Folder 2)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Civic Center, 1991-1993; Series 1 (Box 1464, Folder 3)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Crowne Plaza, 1991-1993; Series 1 (Box 1464, Folder 4)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Financial, 1989-1993; Series 1 (Box 1464, Folder 5)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Fisherman's Wharf, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1464, Folder 6)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Golden Gateway, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1465, Folder 1)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Union Square, 1990-1993; Series 1 (Box 1465, Folder 2)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Hotel Californian, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1465, Folder 3)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Hotel Nikko, 1992-1993; Series 1 (Box 1465, Folder 4)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Hotel Richelieu, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1465, Folder 5)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Hyatt Regency, 1989-1993; Series 1 (Box 1465, Folder 6)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Hyatt Regency-Airport, 1991-1993; Series 1 (Box 1465, Folder 7)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Hyatt Regency-Oakland, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1465, Folder 8)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Mark Hopkins, 1990-1992; Series 1 (Box 1466, Folder 1)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Marriott [file 1/2], 1989-1993; Series 1 (Box 1466, Folder 2)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Marriott [file 2/2], 1989-1993; Series 1 (Box 1466, Folder 3)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Marriott-Fisherman's Wharf, 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 1466, Folder 4)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Pan Pacific Hotel, 1992; Series 1 (Box 1466, Folder 5)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Parc Fifty-Five Hotel [file 1/2], 1988-1993; Series 1 (Box 1466, Folder 6)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Parc Fifty-Five Hotel [file 2/2], 1988-1993; Series 1 (Box 1467, Folder 1)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Park Hyatt, 1992-1993; Series 1 (Box 1467, Folder 2)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Ramada Hotel, 1988-1991; Series 1 (Box 1467, Folder 3)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Ritz-Carlton, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1467, Folder 4)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Sheraton-Fisherman's Wharf, 1991-1993; Series 1 (Box 1467, Folder 5)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Sheraton-Palace Hotel, 1991-1993; Series 1 (Box 1467, Folder 6)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Sheraton-San Francisco Airport, 1991-1993; Series 1 (Box 1467, Folder 7)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Sir Francis Drake on Union Square, 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 1467, Folder 8)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Stanford Court, 1990-1992; Series 1 (Box 1467, Folder 9)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Hotels-Westin St. Francis, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1468, Folder 1)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Magazine, Series 1 (Box 1468, Folder 2)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Maps, Series 1 (Box 1468, Folder 3)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Meeting Room Requests, Series 1 (Box 1468, Folder 4)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Miscellaneous, 1989-1993; Series 1 (Box 1468, Folder 5)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Moscone Center, 1991-1992; Series 1 (Box 1468, Folder 6)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Non-Profit [file 1/3], Series 1 (Box 1468, Folder 7)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Non-Profit [file 2/3], Series 1 (Box 1469, Folder 1)
    Contains a T-shirt.
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Non-Profit [file 3/3], Series 1 (Box 1469, Folder 2)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Past President's Dinner, Series 1 (Box 1469, Folder 3)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Pre-Convention Meetings, 1992-1993; Series 1 (Box 1469, Folder 4)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Program/Platform Guests, 1992-1993; Series 1 (Box 1469, Folder 5)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Programs, Series 1 (Box 1469, Folder 6)
    Contained 2 VHS tapes entitled "131st Annual Meeting Recap Presentation" (June 30-July 5, 1993). The tapes have been removed and placed in the media materials series.
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Project Equality, 1991; Series 1 (Box 1469, Folder 7)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-"R.A. Today" [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1470, Folder 1)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-"R.A. Today" [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1470, Folder 2)